Mss.Ms.Coll.115
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. John Kintzing Kane, 1800-1892; Letters concerning Kane's career as a Philadelphia lawyer and Pennsylvania politician. He was Judge of the U.S. District Court in Pennsylvania, 1846-1854. There is much professional correspondence, as well as a lot of family material, especially concerning 
  - Democratic Citizens of Bradford County, Pa. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1844 August 6
    Invitation.
  - Democratic Committee of Publication, Philadelphia, 1844
    Accounts.
  - Desilver, Robert P. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 January 29
  - Desmond, Daniel I. to "My Dear Sir", 1846 June 18
  - Dewees, Theodore to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1841 June 10
  - Dewees, William P., 1835 January 8
    Will.
  - Dexter, S. Newlin to Hon. John K. Kane, 1856 January 28
  - Dickerson, Mahlon to John K. Kane, Esq., 1836 September 19
  - Dickins, Asbury to Jas. K Kane, Esq., 1834 October 14
  - Diller, A. to J.K. Kane, Esq, 1845 September-1846 January
  - Diller, Isaac R. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845
  - Dobbin, J.C. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1855 February 4
  - Dodson, R.B. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846 February 4
  - Drumm, August to F.R. Shunk, 1846 April 6
  - Drumm, August, et al., 1846 March
    Petition.
  - Duane, W.J. to J.K. Kane, 1831 June 22
  - Duffey, David to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846
  - Dumotton, William to Thomas Caldwell (photocopy), 1821 October 29
  - Dunglison, Robley to J.K. Kane, 1849 February 1
  - Dunham, L.B. to "My Dear Sir", 1845 April 8
  - Dunlap,____ to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1858 February 13
  - Dunlop, F. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1848 April 6
  - DuPonceau, Peter Stephen to John K. Kane, Esq., 1835 November 20
  - Du Val, Gabriel Bertrand to John K. Kane, Esq., 1844-1848
  - Duval, Matilda, 1845
  - Easton (Pa.) Democratic supporters, 1846 January 19
  - Eaton, John H. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1841 November 15
  - Elder, William to J.K. Kane, 1858 January 12
  - Elliott, J.D. to J.H. Eaton, 1841 October 29
  - Elliott, Samuel to Isaac Elliott, 1846 September 11
  - Elwell, Edward to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 December 11
  - English Aggression in Honduras, Undated
  - Everest, G.W. to J.K. Kane, 1845 October 31
  - Everett, Edward to Hon. John K. Kane, 1836-1852
  - Ewing, John H. to Gov. Shunk, 1845 December
  - Faries, Robert to T.L. Kane, 1857
  - Farmers and Mechanicks Bank of Philadelphia., 1857 December 1
    See also: Kane, Elisha Kent. Estate; and, Atkinson, vs. Farmers Bank.
  - Fassett, Schuyler to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 October 22
  - Fausset, John to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841 November 23
  - Fayette County Commissioners to J.K. Kane, 1846 March 9
  - Fegen, John to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 March 2
  - Fern Rock materials, 1857-1858
  - Ferrel, William to Hon. John K. Kane, 1858 January 5
  - Fessett, Schuyler to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 February
  - Findlay, John K. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1844-1845
  - First Troop of Philadelphia Cavalry, Undated
  - Firth, Thomas T. to John K. Kane, 1845 July 22
  - Fisher & Brother to J.P. Green, 1865 September
  - Fisher, C.H. to Judge Kane, Undated
  - Fisher, Joshua Francis to H.D.Gilpin, Undated
  - Fisher, Redwood to H.D. Gilpin, 1832-1836
  - Flagg, A.C. to J.K. Kane Esq., 1840 September-December
  - Flanigan, J.R. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1857 April 18
  - Florence, Thomas B. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1858 January 16
  - Folwell, Robert to Gov. H.R. Shunk, 1846 January 31
  - Forney, John W. to T.L. Kane, 1853 December 17
  - Forney, John W. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1847-1854, undated
  - Forsyth, John to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1836 January 5
  - Foster, Alexander W. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1845 August-1846 February
  - Foster, William B., Jr. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 July 4
  - Fox, George to J.K. Kane, 1831 February 19
  - Fraley, Frederick to John K. Kane, Esq., 1804-1901
  - Franklin, Lady Jane, 1860 November 21
    Autograph.
  - Frazer, John Fries to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1858 January-February
  - Freeland, David S. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1846
  - French, C.G. to Hon J.K. Kane, 1845 May 2
  - Frost, John E. to "Dear Sir", 1833 August 23
  - Galbraith, William A. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 June 29
  - Gemmill, J.M. to A. Boyd Hamilton, 1846 April 24
  - Gerhard, B. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1844, 1853
  - Geyelin, G. to Henry Taylor, 1850 November 1
  - Gilpin, Henry Dilworth to John K. Kane, Esq., 1823-1857
  - Gilpin, Thomas W. to John K Kane, Esq., 1845 July 22
  - Girard Bank, 1845-1846
    Memorial to State Senate and House of Rep. for passage of an Act for the reduction of the Capital Stock of the girard Bank. Assets of Girard Bank April 1845.
  - Girard College, 1835 January 5
    Cost of carving capitals.
  - Girard, Stephen, 1832-1839
    Estate - Marble work done by Struthers.
  - Glossbrenner, A.J. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 April 16
  - Goddard, Charles B. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1834 February 4
  - Goddard, Kingston to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1858 January 19
  - Goodfellow, Henry, 1854
    The facts relating to the separation of the Ship's Company of the Brig. Advance. Written by Henry Goodfellow by command of Miss Bessie Kane. Received August 13, 1973 - Gift of Mrs. E. Paul DuPont
  - Graff, Charles to Hon. John K. Kane, 1831 August-1832 April
  - Graham, G.W. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 April 24
  - Graham, John to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846 February 18
  - Gray, Joseph to Gov. Shunk, 1845 November 20
  - Greeley, Horace to "My Dear Kane", 1849 July 27
  - Green, A. to Francis Wharton, 1845 January 18
  - Green, John P. to Mrs. J.D.L. Kane, 1862-1863
  - _______ to Hon. John P. Green, 1857-1859
  - Greig, John to John K. Kane, Esq., 1844-1858
  - Greig, Joseph, 1845 November 20
  - Grey, William to F.R. Shunk, 1845 September 29
  - Grier, R.C. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846-1854, undated
  - Grier, R.C. to J.C. Molloy, 1853 November 14
  - Griffin, S.P. to Hon. Judge Kane, 1855 March 12
  - Grinnell, Henry to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1851-1856, undated
  - Grotten, Joseph to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1849 February 8
  - Guillere to Mr. Sheppard, 1865 September
  - Guillou, Constant to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1846
  - Guillou, Constant to Mrs. Kane, May 13
  - Gwin, Alen to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846 May 13
  - Gwin, James to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846 April 24
  - Hague, Thomas to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 April 11
  - Hamburger, Herman to J.P. Green, 1861 August 26
  - Hamilton, Alexander to R. Morris, 1790 March 19
  - Hamilton, Mrs. A. to George Washington, Undated
    A photocopy of a fragmant. Returned to Mr. T.C. Cope - 1969 November 11.
  - Hamilton, Elizabeth (Mrs. Alexander), Undated
  - Hamilton, William to Mr. Caldwell, 1821 October 29
    Also, a cure for convulsions.
  - Harris, George W. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1830 October 11
  - Harris, Thomas to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 April -1849 December
  - Harris, Thomas to J.A. Kearny, 1846 February 9
  - Harrison, Sophia to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 December 27
  - Hartz, David to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1846 February-March
  - Hatcher, Lewis M. to Judge J.K. Kane, 1858 February 2
  - Hawes, Horace to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1846
  - Hayes, P. Barry to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1845 April 14
  - Hayes, S.B. to F.R .Shunk, 1846 January 5
  - Helme, S.P. to W.J. Leiper, 1841 February 4
  - Hepburn, Joseph to Hon. J.K. Kane, November 17
  - Hickman, John to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1846 July-September
  - Hieskell, W.B. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841 December 30
  - Hildeburn, Henry M. to W.H. Weaver, 1849 December 23
  - Hilgard, Julius Erasmus to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1849 April-1858 January
  - Hillman, Joseph, et al, Undated
  - Hilsmann, Heinrich to Friedrich Hilsmann, 1805 July 28
  - Hinds, C.H. to William Word, 1857 January 8
  - Hinton, H.A. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 October 8
  - Hirst, W.L. to J.K. Kane, February 14
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania to John K. Kane Esq., 1844 July 3
  - Hitchcock, L.P. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1846 January 5
  - Hobart, John H. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1846
  - Hodge, Langford Lovell to John K. Kane, Esq., 1842 October 18
  - Hoe, M.S., Mrs. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 October
  - Hoelker, L. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1825-1837
  - Hollingsworth, Henry to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1847 January 19
  - Hopkins, William to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 August 9
  - Hopkinson, Francis to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1846 October 26
  - Hopkinson, Francis, et al, 1843 November 13
  - Hopkinson, J. to J.K. Kane, Undated
  - Horn, Henry to J.K. Kane, 1844 July 11
  - Horn, J.O. to G.M. Dallas, 1844 July 17
  - Houston, J.W. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 March 27
    Folder includes letter from the Mayamensing Bank, Philadelphia to J.W. Houston, Esq.
  - Houston, Samuel to J.K. Kane, 1825? May 25
  - Howard to Hon John K. Kane, 1846 February 6
  - Hubbell, Ferdinand W. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1846
  - Hughes, J.J. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841 August 30
  - Indian Rights Association, 1892
  - Indigent Widows and Single Women's Society, 1866 January 4
    Report.
  - Ingersoll, Edward to John F. Gibson, 1828 October 3
  - Ingersoll, Joseph R. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1847-1848
  - Ingersoll, R.I. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1844 August 16
  - Ingham, Samuel D. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1829-1854
  - Ingraham, A., et al, April 12
  - Irvine, W.P. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 April 2
  - Irving, Washington to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 March 1
  - Irving, Washington, Undated
  - Irwin, J. Andie to J.K. Kane, 1845 November 11
  - Irwin, J.R. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 February 21
  - Irwin, John to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 June 12
  - Jackson, Andrew to Henry Simpson, et al, 1837 January 4
    President of the United States. (facsimile)
  - Jackson, G.W. to A.B. Hamilton, 1846 April 19
  - Janeway, J.J. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1840-1853
  - Janeway, J.J. to Mrs. Kane, 1852
  - Jayne, W.S. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1745 November 26
  - Jessup, William Y. to William Strickland, 1834 October 3
  - Jessup, William Y. to John K. Kane Esq., 1836 June 16
  - Joachimssen, P.I. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841
  - Johnson, C. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1846 November 8
  - Johnson, Charles to John K. Kane, Esq., March 19
  - Johnson, O.F. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 August 8
  - Johnson, T.W. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1845 November 28
  - Jones, Joel to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 January 24
  - Jones, J.P. to J.K. Kane, 1845 November 6
  - Jones, M. Hale to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845
  - Jones, Nathan to John Bartram, 1795 March 11
    Bond.
  - Jones, Nathan to Margaret Robert, 1820 May 30
  - Jordan, A. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 May 27
  - Judson, L.C. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1845 December 11
  - Justus, Philip, et al to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1846 January 21
  - Kane, Alida V.R. to John Kintzing Kane, 1820 August 12
  - Kane, Bessie to Dr. J.K. Kane, Jr., August 18
  - Kane, Bessie to Dr. John K. Kane, Jr., Undated
  - Kane, C.V.S. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841
  - Kane, E.D., Mrs. to J.P. Green, Undated
  - Kane, E.K. to Bessie Kane, 1848 July 4
  - Kane, Elias K. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1819 December; 1829 February
  - Kane, Elias Kent to John K. Kane, Esq., 1825-1834
  - Kane, Elias Kent to Elisha Kane, 1829 January 16
  - Kane, Elisha Kent to John K. Kane, Esq., 1824-1829
  - Kane, Elizabeth D. to Elizabeth K. Kane (mother), 1857 September
  - Kane, Elizabeth D. to J.P. Green, 1857-1858
  - Kane, Elizabeth F to 'My dear mother', 1864 August 30
  - Kane, Elizabeth F. to Mrs Kane (mother), Undated
  - Kane, Elizabeth Kintzing (mother) to John Kintzing Kane (son), 1817-1825
    Letters from mother of John K. Kane.
  - Kane Family genealogy, Undated
  - Kane, Francis Fisher to W.H. Brawley, 1892 March 15
  - Kane, James to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846-1851
  - Kane, James to Mrs. James D.L. Kane, 1846 June 17
  - Kane, James to Mrs. Sally Morris, 1847 June 29
  - Kane, Jane Duval Leiper, Mrs. to Mrs. Bessie (Elizabeth) Kane Shields, 1849-1868
  - Kane, Jane Duval Leiper, Mrs. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1825
  - Kane, Jane Duval Leiper, Mrs. to Dr. John K. Kane, Jr., Undated
  - Kane, Jane Duval Leiper, Mrs. to W.H. Weaver, 1850
  - Kane, J.K., Undated
    American Philosophical Society material in re "Junto"
  - Kane, J.K., 1844 June
    Biographical notes on G.M. Dallas.
  - Kane, J.K., 1841 October 18
    Concerning treatment of the insane, (copy)
  - Kane, J.K., 1854 December 1
    Eulogy for R.M. Patterson for American Philosophical Society.
  - Kane, J.K., 1823 May 22
    Indenture....Presbyterian Ministers Fund.
  - Kane, J.K., undated
    List of Deeds executed.
  - Kane, J.K., 1847 March 6
    Memoranda.
  - Kane, J.K., Undated
    Prison reform.
  - Kane, J.K., 1841 April 30
    Sale of Library Company of Philadelphia share to Elisha K. Kane.
  - Kane, J.K., Undated
    Speech to the American Philosophical Society.
  - Kane, J.K., 1845 April
    Veto message for the Girard Bank Bill, written for Gov. Shunk.
  - Kane, J.K., 1847 March 27
  - Kane, J.K. to J.W. Ashmead & G. Randle, 1842 October 15
  - Kane, J.K. to A.D. Bache, 1857 October 24
  - Kane, J.K. to Gen. Barnard, 1829 October 28
  - Kane, J.K. to William Paul Crillon Barton, 1842 June 2; 9-7/8x8
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. Verifying birth date of his son Elisha Kent Kane.
  - Kane, J.K. to Democratic Citizens of Bradford County, 1844 August
  - Kane, J.K. to Mr. Draper, 1857 June
  - Kane, J.K. to John Dubarry, 1824 April 21
  - Kane, J.K. to editor, Undated
  - Kane, J.K. to Dr. William Elder, 1857 August 19?
    Notes written about Elisha K Kane's youth, education, and sea voyages as a surgeon aboard naval ships. Description of Eastern Andes of Brazil, India, Ceylon, China, Island of Luson, Egypt, Africa. Description of slave mart in Dahomey (Africa) and predatory wars of inner Africa amongst chieftains that sought for prisoners as victims of sacrifice.
  - Kane, J.K. to John K. Findlay, January 4
  - Kane, J.K. to F. Fraley, 1853 September 15
  - Kane, J.K. to H.D. Gilpin, 1825-1856
  - Kane, J.K. to R.C. Grier, 1854-1858
  - Kane, J.K. to H. Grinnell, 1854-1855
  - Kane, J.K. to John S. Hart, 1843 October 26
  - Kane, J.K. to Charles F. Heazlitt, 1855 July 18
  - Kane, J.K. to L.L. Hodge, 1832 November 8
  - Kane, J.K. to F. Hopkinson, 1846 October 23
  - Kane, J.K. to Mrs. S.B. Hughes, 1832 March 31
  - Kane, J.K. to Mr. Ingham, 1844 November 23
  - Kane, J.K. to Elias K. Kane, 1829 September 26
  - Kane, J.K. to Mrs. Jane D.L. Kane, 1833 February 4
  - Kane, J.K. to Theodore Kane, 1841 June 1
  - Kane, J.K. to T.L. Kane, 1838 January 1
  - Kane, J.K. to W.J. Leiper, 1835-1857
  - Kane, J.K. to W.M. Meredith, 1832 November 15
  - Kane, J.K. to Jesse Miller, 1846 March 30
  - Kane, J.K. to John S. Mumford, 1844 August 30
  - Kane, J.K. to Mrs. Helen Patterson, 1830 July 23
  - Kane, J.K. to W. Phelps, 1848 June 14
  - Kane, J.K. to Pres. Pierce, 1854 November 9
  - Kane, J.K. to Mr. Price, 1854 March 29
  - Kane, J.K. to S.E. Rice, 1831 August 2
  - Kane, J.K. to Bessie Kane Shields, 1842-1847
  - Kane, J.K. to F.R. Shunk, 1845
  - Kane, J.K. to Mrs. A. Van Rensselaer, Constable, 1834-1841
  - Kane, J.K. to H.I. Williams, 1843 November
  - Kane, J.K. to J.W. Wood, 1858 November 5
  - Kane, J.K. to ________, 1857
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Account of a dance, Undated
    First page missing
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Arctic Diary (photocopy), Undated
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Notes on Arctic voyage #1 (photocopies), 1857 May - 1858 April
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Notes on Arctic voyage #2 (photcopies), 1857 May - 1858 April
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Notes on Arctic voyage #3 (photcopies), 1857 May - 1858 April
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Notes on Arctic voyage #4 (photocopies), 1857 May - 1858 April
  - Kane, J.K., Jr. to Bessie Kane, 1851 November 18
  - Kane, J.K., Jr. to Kane family, 1852-1862
  - Kane, J.K., Jr. to J.K. Kane & family, 1857 - 1858
  - Kane, J.K., Jr. to mother and father, 1852-1856
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- note, Undated
    Address: Arctic Expedition
  - Kane, J.K., Jr. to Robert Patterson Kane, August 23
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Passport, 1857 May 22
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- Private journal, 1855
    United States Arctic Expedition - U S Steam Brig "Arctic" - in search of Dr Elisha Kane by order of congress. Under command of Captain Hartstein.
  - Kane, J.K., Jr. to Bessie Kane Shields, 1861 March 22
  - Kane, J.K., Jr.- A Summer's Trip to the Arctic Region, 1856 May
    For Putnam's Magazine.
  - Kane, J.L. to Elizabeth Kane, 1843 August 9
  - Kane, John to Elisha Kane, December 28
  - ______ to John K. Kane, Esq., 1840-1848
  - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1858
    Regarding death of J.K. Kane - estate of Thomas L. Kane
  - Kane, Robert Patterson to mother and father, 1857
  - Kane, Robert van Rensselaer to Elisha Kane, 1810 December 19
  - Kane, Robert van Rensselaer to Mrs. E.K. Kane, Undated
  - Kane, Theodore to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841 May 29
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to family, 1845-1857
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to John K. Kane Esq., 1831-1857
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to Hon. John K. Kane, 1857 February 20
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to Dr. John K. Kane, Jr., 1868 July 3
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to W.J. Leiper, 1846 July
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to Mr. Merrick, 1857 May 23
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper to P.M. Price, 1856-1857
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper- recommendations, 1846 June 11
  - Kane, William L. to Thomas L. Kane, May 8
  - Kearney, John A. to B. Franklin Bache, 1844 December
  - Kearney, John A. to David Henshaw, 1844 April
  - Keim, George M. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 June
  - Kelley, William D. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 December 31
  - Kendall, Amos to H.D. Gilpin, 1839 October 26
  - Kent, Edward to the representatives of the late Dr. Kane, 1866 March
    Letter addressed: "To the representatives of the late doctor Kane of world-wide fame. Or of his great grandfather the Rev Elisha Kent formerly of Massachusetts. America"
  - King, John P. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1844
  - Kinney, W.C. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1844 August 7
  - Kirkbride, Thomas S. to John K. Kane, Esq., Undated
  - Kline, George M. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 August 7
  - Kossuth, L. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1851 December 31
  - Kurtz, W.H. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 April 12
  - Laporte, John to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845-1848
  - Latrobe, John Hazlehurst Boneval to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1849 November 10
  - Laughlin, H.H. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1844 May 30
  - Law, John to "My dear Kane", 1845 March 11
  - Law, John to Daniel Lord, 1839 August 5
  - Lehigh Coal and Navigation Company, 1844 November 14
  - Leiper, George G., et al - agreement, Undated; Leiper, George Gray, 1786-1868
  - Leiper, Mary B. to Judge Kane, 1857
  - Leiper, Mary B. to Mr. Clay, 1858 March 19
  - Leiper, Mary B. to "My Dear Sister", March 11; Leiper, Mary B.
  - Leiper, Mrs.- account with receipts, 1854
  - Leiper, Samuel M. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 March 9
    See also: Coffin, William; Lex, C. F., et al; and, Franklin Fire Insurance Company of Philadelphia.
  - Leiper, Samuel M. to Mrs. J.D.L. Taylor, 1852 April 19
  - Leiper, Thomas- estate, 1842
  - Leiper, William Jones to John K. Kane, Esq., 1826, 1844-1846
  - Lemon, P. and W.S. Jayne to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 September 29
  - Lewis, Ellis to John K. Kane, Esq., 1843 April 10
  - Lewis, George T. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1852 November 19
  - Lewis, R.M. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1833-1834
  - Lewis, William D. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1840-1845
  - Linn, L.F., Undated
    Autographs - franking privilege.
  - List, Christopher to F.R. Shunk, 1846 January 26
  - Little and Elwell to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 September 18
  - Livermore, D. to Hon. John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 December 21
  - Livingston, J.K. to Hon. J.K. Kane, 1846 October 5
  - Livingston, R. Dwight to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 November 19
  - Longacre, Henry C.- recommendation, Oct 2
  - Longstreth, Morris to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845-1846
  - Lord, B. to Stephen Baldwin, 1838 January 10
  - Lowrie, J. Roberts to J.N. Purviance, 1846 April 27
  - MacArthur, Mrs. Mary Hess to Hon John K Kane, 1846 March 23
  - MacGregor, Daniel to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846
  - Mackubin, James to W.H. Weaver, 1849-1850
  - Macmanus, James to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 April 8
  - Madiera, Louis C. to J.K. Kane, 1845 November 25
  - Madison, G.A. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1833 December 5
  - Magdalen Society, 1845 September 8
    Extract from minutes.
  - Maiset, John M. to Henry Bower, 1865 January 4
  - Mano, Henry to John K. Kane, Esq., 1850 October 29
  - Mapes, Elsworth to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 February 21
  - Marcy, W.L. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1854 March 20
  - Marshall, James C. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 February 23
  - Massachusetts, Governor to Judge Kane, 1847 August 24
  - Mathiot, W. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845-1846
  - Matthew, G. to "Dear Sir", February 12
  - Maury, Matthew Fontaine to "My dear Sir", 1858 January 1
  - McAlester, Charles to John K. Kane, Esq., 1841
  - McAllister, Richard to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1853
  - McCahen, John J. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 April 2
  - McCall, Archibald to J.K. Kane, 1835 June 2
  - McCall, Henry to Hon. Judge Kane, 1812
  - McCall, M.M. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1841 November 4
  - McCall, P. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845 August 14
  - McCall, Peter to J.K. Drinker, 1828 April 7
  - McCauley, J.H. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 March 5
  - McClean, Moses to Henry Welsh, 1845 May 5
  - McClintock, J.R. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 January 26
  - McCorkell, William & Co. to Robert Taylor & Co., 1849 April 12
  - McCracken, Henry F. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1859 February 3
  - McCulloch, James William to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 November 3
  - McDowell, T. Crawford to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 May 21
  - McIlvaine, Henry to president of ______ society, 1846 January 9
  - McKim, J.M. to Col. Thomas L. Kane, 1854 July 19
  - McLanahan, James K. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 May 9
  - McLane, Allen M. to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1837 May 18
  - McLane, Louis to John K. Kane, Esq., 1827-1833
  - McLeod, William N. to R. Dunglison, 1840 January 8
  - McMicken, J.S. to Leiper Patterson, Undated
  - McMurtrie, W.V., et al to John K. Kane, Esq., Undated
  - Mercantile Library Company, Philadelphia., 1841 May 10
  - Meredith, W.M. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1832-1849
  - Meriam, Ebenezer to Dr.John Kane, Jr., 1855 May 30
  - Merrill, G.A. to "My dear Mr. Kane", 1892 December 31
  - Miles, Thomas J. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 November 29
  - Mill, John to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846 May 2
  - Mill, Peter J. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846 January 22
  - Millen, John J. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1846
  - Miller, A.J. and T.W. Miller to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1845 October 11
  - Miller, Andrew to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1846
  - Miller, J. to David Hartz, 1845 March 4
  - Miller, J. Craig to John K. Kane, Esq., 1846
  - Miller, Jesse to John K. Kane, Esq., 1845-1848
  - Miller, Peter to Hon. John K. Kane, 1848 June 14
  - Miscellaneous
  - Mitchell, E.D. to J.P. Green, Undated
  - Mitchell, J. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 April 20
  - Mitchell, J.K. to J.K. Kane, Esq., Undated
  - Montgomery, William to Hon. John K. Kane, 1845 December 10
  - Moore, Thomas to J.K. Kane, Esq., 1835 May 11
  - Morgan, Thomas P. to Hon. John K. Kane, 1854 September 20
  - Morris, Governor to Robert Morris, 1793
    Orginals returned to Mr T C Cope - 1969 Nov 11
  - Morris, Henry W. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1843-1845
  - Morris, Robert to Thomas Morris, 1797
  - Morris, Sally to Judge Kane and James Kane, Esq., 1847-1850
  - Morris, Thomas to John K. Kane, Esq., 1842-1843
  - Morris, Thomas, Mrs. to John K. Kane, 1851 October 6
    Typed transcript with title "A letter from Mrs. Thomas Morris to her nephew the Hon. Judge John K. Kane, regarding the Kane and Kent familites, etc."
  - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese to Mr. Gifford, 1851 January 1
  - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese to George Harding, 1851 October 30
  - Moss, Joseph S. and E.L. Moss to Struthers and Son, 1841-1842
  - Muffley, J.L. to Jerman Hamburger, 1862 July 10
  - Muhlenberg, Henry Augustus to W.J. Leiper, 1843 September 28
  - Mumford, John I. to John K. Kane, Esq., 1844 August
  - Murchison, Sir Roderick Impey to G.M. Dallas, 1857 July 7
  - Musical Fund Society, 1839 July 1